<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on GIS 4 Labrador</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on GIS 4 Labrador</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 10:51:34 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberSecurity</title>
      <link>/post/cybersecurity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2019 19:08:27 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/cybersecurity/</guid>
      <description>CyberSecurity makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 Tor Browser Tor Project - Protect yourself against tracking, surveillance, and censorship How HTTPS and Tor Work Together to Protect Your Anonymity and Privacy Detailed VPN Comparison Chart Protect your Privacy with a VPN Tunnel WhatIsMyIP.com Mullvad Tunnelblick free software for OpenVPN on macOS OpenVPN Algo VPN Fast Internet Archive  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tablau</title>
      <link>/post/tablau/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 15:42:31 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/tablau/</guid>
      <description>Tablau makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 Visual Analysis Best Practices Create Charts with Tableau Public Tablau - Popular Topics A buffet of materials to help get you started, or take you to the next level  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kartograph</title>
      <link>/post/kartograph/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 15:04:06 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/kartograph/</guid>
      <description>Kartograph makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 Kartograph  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google_Drive</title>
      <link>/post/google_drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 12:34:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/google_drive/</guid>
      <description>Google drive makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 Match Columns with VLOOKUP REMOVING DUPLICATE ROWS OPEN REFINE AND A DATASET Chart Your Data Google Sheets function list  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book</title>
      <link>/post/book/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 09:48:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/book/</guid>
      <description>Book makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 On The Line: How Schooling, Housing, and Civil Rights Shaped Hartford and its Suburbs How to Lie with Statistics How to Lie with Maps, 2nd ed. (University of Chicago Press, 1996) Storytelling with Data: A Data Visualization Guide for Business Professionals (Wiley, 2015)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job</title>
      <link>/post/job/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 12:40:47 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/job/summary/</guid>
      <description>Job makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 A Career in Cartography? The Remote Freelancer Geospatial Jobs How I Became A Digital Nomad 79 Websites To Get Freelance Jobs Fast 20 TIPS FOR GREAT JOB INTERVIEWS  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog</title>
      <link>/post/blog/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:25:24 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/blog/summary/</guid>
      <description>Blog makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 Anita Graser Spatial Galaxy Maps Mania City Lab Google Maps Map of the week Carto Talk Learn practical web skills courses GIS User Revolutionary GIS J-Reading - Journal of Research and Didactics in Geography World of Satellites at your fingertips Matthew Toro Helpful Digital Lutra consulting The Most Densely Populated Square Kilometre in 39 European Countries GIS for Thought Paul Ramsey SpatialDB Advisor Il mondo del web a 360 gradi VisiData: il coltellino svizzero per i dati, che probabilmente non conosci LEARN GIS ATLANTE STATISTICO DEI COMUNI EDIZIONE 2019 Training Materials for Classes - Datapolitan Loading Open Addresses Data into PostGIS Digital Resources Earth Observation and GIS blog categories The 2018 Web Developer Roadmap Open Geo Hub Geo Republic Association for Geographic Information, promoting geospatial &amp;hellip; Robin&amp;rsquo;s Blog North River Geographic Systems, Inc Getpostman Geotoolsnews THE BLOG OF A DATA SCIENTIST&amp;rsquo;S JOURNEY gisinfrastrutture itopen SPATIAL THOUGHTS OpenGIS CH ISPRS International Journal of Geo-Information — Open Access Journal Source is an OpenNews project Learn to visualize your data like an expert with these practical how-tos for presentation, analysis, and understanding Joshua Stevens Mapzen Storytelling with Data Spatial {Query} Lab geospatial technologies and practices gvSIG blog  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Machine</title>
      <link>/post/virtualmachine/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:24:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/virtualmachine/summary/</guid>
      <description>Virtual Machine makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 XAMPP WAMPSERVER MAMP  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scraping</title>
      <link>/post/scraping/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:24:44 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/scraping/summary/</guid>
      <description>Scraping makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 How to scrape businesses’ info with Python and Beautiful Soup Espressioni regolari un regex classico []() []() []() []() []() []() []() []() []() []() []() []() []() []() []() []() []() []() []() []() []() []() []()  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git&amp;GitHub</title>
      <link>/post/git_github/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:24:27 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/git_github/summary/</guid>
      <description>Git&amp;amp;GitHub makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 Nathaniel V. KELSO Mappiamo Vega Edition Vega Edition What is GitHub Pages? Learn Enough Git to be Useful 10 Git Commands You Should Know Learn Git with Bitbucket Cloud T&amp;rsquo;ansignari e t&amp;rsquo;appeddiri! Learning to code in 2019 — the first 3 months Your unofficial guide to dotfiles on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scripts</title>
      <link>/post/script/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:23:19 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/script/summary/</guid>
      <description>Script makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 How Do I Download an Entire Website for Offline Reading? 13 siti utili Bash Scripting Scaricare tutti i bollettini sulla qualità dell’aria del comune di Palermo Espressioni regolari per la pulizia dei dati Bulk Rename Utility Introduction to the geo command line  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenStreetMap</title>
      <link>/post/openstreetmap/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:23:03 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/openstreetmap/summary/</guid>
      <description>OpenStreetMap makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 Learn OSM Download OpenStreetMap data for this region: You can help. Map any place in the world even if you&amp;rsquo;ve never been there. Why would you use OpenStreetMap if there is Google Maps? Overpass API Manual custom geocoding using OSM database Near real-time OpenStreetMap editing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geocode</title>
      <link>/post/geocode/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:22:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/geocode/summary/</guid>
      <description>Geocode makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 Geocode Locations into Coordinates with US Census or Google QGIS - How to Geocode Addresses Using QGIS How to quickly add latitude and longitude coordinates to a spreadsheet using Google Sheets Python Geocode ESRI  ArcGIS PRO Geocode a table of addresses ArcGIS Geocoding Tutorial Data Introduction to locator roles  Batch CSV Geocoding in Python with Google Maps API Developer Guide - Google Maps This is overpass turbo, a web-based data filtering tool for OpenStreetMap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Licence</title>
      <link>/post/licences/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:22:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/licences/summary/</guid>
      <description>Licence makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 Conformant Licenses Understanding Free Cultural Works Licensing types Linked Data Open data in Italia Choose an open source license Licensing a repository  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GoogleMaps</title>
      <link>/post/googlemaps/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:21:35 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/googlemaps/summary/</guid>
      <description>GoogleMaps makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 Maps Mania Using Google Maps costs more than you think. Place Autocomplete Address Form Visualizing Geographic Statistical Data with Google Maps Prototyping a Smoother Map Come erano Italia ed Europa nell&amp;rsquo;800, ecco Google Maps &amp;lsquo;vintage&amp;rsquo; Gmaps Heatmap Layer Plugin Geocoding Tutorial using Google Fusion Tables Fusion Tables Workshop How to quickly add latitude and longitude coordinates to a spreadsheet using Google Sheets Places Search Box Geocoding + Location Columns in Google Fusion Tables Google Maps APIs byGoogle Using Google Maps API (v3) with Rails (5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>D3</title>
      <link>/post/d3/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:21:14 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/d3/summary/</guid>
      <description>D3 makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 A Primer in D3js for the Curious D3 gallery D3 Workshop Introduction to D3 - Make a Chart Scatterplots and Borrowing Code Interaction and Animation: D3 Transitions, Behaviors, and Brushing Mapping Data with D3 Tutorial The America’s Cup Finale: Oracle’s Path to Victory Fast, static D3 maps built with Turf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mapbox</title>
      <link>/post/mapbox/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:21:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/mapbox/summary/</guid>
      <description>Mapbox makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 Mapbox How To Start Doh! Making a Simpsons-inspired map with expressions Exploring the edges of consumer-facing apps Mapbox helps power Snap Map Build beautiful experiences and drive engagement Traveling like a local: How Cool Cousin uses maps to personalize travel Locate Mapbox UNICEF’s Magic Box Using Open Source by Red Hat and Uber and Big Data by Facebook to Map for Emergencies map viewer  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leaflet</title>
      <link>/post/leaflet/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:20:54 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/leaflet/summary/</guid>
      <description>Leaflet makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 Leaflet Map Templates Leaflet Day 14 - Image Overlay and Wrap-up Leaflet for R Geolocate User Location in R Leaflet Geolocate User Location in R Leaflet Shiny APP Publishing Maps Creating a Leaflet Map and publishing it on RPubs Leaflet: Make a web map! leaflet-omnivore Leaflet and Mapbox JavaScript API Fundamentals Rendering table Heatmap Mappa carina Plugin wordpress ROADS TO ROME Free Course Mapping with leaflet PostGIS + Geoserver + Leaflet: mini tutorial Mapsmarker Publishing Maps to the Web All lessons provided by NCEAS and collaborators here on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SQL</title>
      <link>/post/sql/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:20:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/sql/summary/</guid>
      <description>SQL makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 Modern SQL Mission LiteCLI è un client a riga di comando per hashtag#SQLite con autocompletamento (anche fuzzy) e syntax highlighting W3Schools - SQL Tutorial SQL API v2 The SQL UPDATE Statement Welcome Non-key Columns in B-Tree Indexes SQL/JSON Path Expressions  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video</title>
      <link>/post/video/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:20:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/video/</guid>
      <description>Video makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 13 APP PER FARE VIDEO GRATIS  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ElasticSearch</title>
      <link>/post/elasticsearch/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:20:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/elasticsearch/summary/</guid>
      <description>*ElasticSearch makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 []() []() []() []() []()  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript</title>
      <link>/post/javascript/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:20:03 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/javascript/summary/</guid>
      <description>JavaScript makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 noUiSlider A JSON Tutorial. Getting started with JSON using JavaScript and jQuery jsfiddle World Turn your Gephi data into an interactive website map - Helpful Digital JavaScript GEXF Viewer for Gephi World Map of Social Networks Social Media Statistic Custom Interactive Maps heatmap.js Examples MapStore Creare dashboard con Superset 11 Javascript Data Visualization Libraries for 2019 Free Clip Art You Can Use For Anything You Like Welcome to the Magic Box wiki!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Text Editor</title>
      <link>/post/editor/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:19:34 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/editor/summary/</guid>
      <description>Text Editor makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 Sublime Text Brackets Notepad++ TextWrangler Adobe Dreamweaver JSFiddle: Javascript coding playground. Bootply: Bootstrap coding playground.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fonts</title>
      <link>/post/font/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:18:54 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/font/summary/</guid>
      <description>Fonts makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 Adobe Fonts dafont whatfontis Font Awesome  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Illustrator</title>
      <link>/post/illustrator/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:18:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/illustrator/summary/</guid>
      <description>Illustrator makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 Creating a Map with Illustrator Mappe topografiche in legno uniche e artigianali Maps - Marcel Morin How to Create an Informative Map In Perspective with Illustrator Open Vector Maps color adobe TerraServer Mapquest Mapquest Intro to Adobe Illustrator Adobe Creative Cloud Kelso&amp;rsquo;s Cartography and Graphic Design Scripts for Adobe Illustrator Scripts for automating Adobe Illustrator Mapping with Adobe CC  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>API</title>
      <link>/post/api/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:18:31 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/api/summary/</guid>
      <description>API makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 Best Practices for Designing a Pragmatic RESTful API Free and Open Source Public Web CDN for web developer! Navermaps Converting OpenAPI specs to Postman collections 10+ Best jQuery Geolocation Plugins &amp;amp; Tutorials with Demo 10+ Best jQuery Geolocation Plugins &amp;amp; Tutorials with Demo Travel time Socrata  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebGIS</title>
      <link>/post/webgis/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:18:07 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/webgis/summary/</guid>
      <description>WebGIS makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1cQcuJY7KK0BLfu7DBWSUdgPd-rXOmouX18UL1Z7sQqY/edit#gid=239928523/gviz/tq?tq=select%A
Introduction
 Online mapping tools uMap uMap Luca MAPWARPER Tutorial per creare mappe online su UMAP aggiornabili con file CSV da GOOGLEDRIVE Query Language Kepler Teaching Digital Mapping with kepler.gl kepler.gl - Tutorial Mapstarter is a tool for turning a geographic data file into a map for the web</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOSS4G</title>
      <link>/post/foss4g/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:17:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/foss4g/summary/</guid>
      <description>FOSS4G makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 OSGeo Annual General Meeting 2018 Boston 2017 FOSS for GIS video tutorials and screencasts Events History Italia Foss4g-It 2019 foss4g-oceania Foss4g-it abstract Slides FOSS4G-IT 2019  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python</title>
      <link>/post/python/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:17:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/python/summary/</guid>
      <description>Python makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 Automating GIS processes course! Automating GIS processes Geo libraries in Python (Plotting current fires) Satellite Imagery Analysis with Python PyQGIS 101: Introduction to QGIS Python programming for non-programmers Pyimagesearch Advanced Jupyter Notebooks: A Tutorial Really Simple HTTP Server with Python Python for Geospatial work flows, part 3: Virtual Environments From CSV to GeoDataFrame in two lines Dataset creation and cleaning: Web Scraping using Python — Part 1 Intro to Python and Pandas Intro to Python and Web Scraping Movement data in GIS #20: Trajectools v1 released!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carto</title>
      <link>/post/carto/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:17:08 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/carto/summary/</guid>
      <description>Carto makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 Mobile Data 101: 15 Questions to Answer Using Mobile Data Set up an account on CARTO CARTO’s SQL API Editing East Coast Greenway Route in QGIS CartoDB plugin for QGIS CartoDB plugin for QGIS Mapping and Planning the East Coast Greenway Mobile Data 101: Challenges and Best Practices Exporting Maps for Printing in the Digital Maps Era Supercharging your Site Selection: CARTO Reveal&amp;rsquo;s latest release Point Map with Carto Builder  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud</title>
      <link>/post/cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:17:08 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/cloud/</guid>
      <description>Cloud makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 Digital Ocean Amazon Boundless  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GDAL</title>
      <link>/post/gdal/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:16:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/gdal/summary/</guid>
      <description>GDAL makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 Setting up GDAL Batch Mode Equivalent of .bat in mac os Converting between KML and shapefile (SHP) format? Bulk SHP/KML Processing Tools ogr2ogr Quick Start Guide GDAL/OGR Quickstart Converting GIS Vector Data to KML GDAL - Feature Style Specification To convert multiple kml file (googleearth layer) to shapefile with QGIS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PostGIS</title>
      <link>/post/postgis/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:16:35 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/postgis/summary/</guid>
      <description>PostGIS makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 Introduction to PostGIS Why should you care about PostGIS? — A gentle introduction to spatial databases Query in DB-fiddle How I go about teaching JOINs to people Installazione di PostgreSQL11/PostGIS su macOS (e Linux) via Homebrew. Il terminale interattivo- psql Spatial Database Management Bye bye Mongo, Hello Postgres pgRouting Official Documentation Using PostGIS: Data Management and Queries PostGIS Reference 2D distance between points Operators ST_MakePoint Spatial Reference Systems ST_SetSRID Creating a Geospatial database on Amazon RDS Places and their names — observations from 11 million place names PostGIS Spatial Function Practice Exercise Solutions Introduction to PostGIS PostGIS Training Course Which African country has the most number of neighbours?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spatialite</title>
      <link>/post/spatialite/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:16:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/spatialite/summary/</guid>
      <description>SpatiaLite makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 SpatiaLite []() []() []() []() []() []() []() []() []()  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ArcGIS</title>
      <link>/post/arcgis/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:15:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/arcgis/summary/</guid>
      <description>ArcGIS makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 GitHub Learn ArcGIS includes 17 lessons featuring ArcGIS Pro Beginner&amp;rsquo;s guide to Python in ArcGIS Pro, Part 1: Why? Welcome to GeoNet, the Esri Community! Excel Map Hack Exercises and data for the book
 Learn ArcGIS
 What&amp;rsquo;s New in ArcGIS
 Finding Data on ArcGIS Hub Open Data Portal</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QGIS</title>
      <link>/post/qgis/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:15:32 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/qgis/summary/</guid>
      <description>QGIS makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 GitHub Building QGIS from source - step by step QField per QGIS - Release Candidate 4 OpenRouteService QGIS e il globo terrestre QGIS 3.4 shortcuts guide How to add Google Maps layers in QGIS 3 Help funzioni calcolatore di campi di QGIS MMQGIS Università Empoli Animate plugin DTM - curve di livello GeoPackage OSM Tools plugin in QGIS  Tutorials</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GIS</title>
      <link>/post/gis/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:15:14 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/gis/summary/</guid>
      <description>GIS makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
MOOC da inserire!!!
Introduction
 Cartographic design principles Map Design in GIS (theory) MAPPABLE CHEAT-SHEET 14 Common UX Mistakes Generative Street Addresses from Satellite Imagery LandGISmaps Geospatial Analysis - A comprehensive guide - 2018 Why GIS in Education Matters GeoHack - Geographical centre of all land surfaces on Earth Open Education Resources Free Urban Planning GIS Exercises Open Access book  Tutorials</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can your customers find you?</title>
      <link>/post/scribblemaps/can_your_customers_find_you/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 12:21:24 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/scribblemaps/can_your_customers_find_you/</guid>
      <description>The Christmas holidays are upon us. It’s time for shopping and relaxation. Commercial activities are in full swing. Advertisements flood TV, newspapers, and radio with a ton of last-minute promotions.
If you are a new business and you would like to advertise an event to attract new customers, you will sure to be found.
Scribble Maps will make your life easier and help you create a map that can be shared on your digital channels, like social media, your website, and WhatsApp, with directions to your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geomarketing Market Research</title>
      <link>/post/scribblemaps/geomarketing_market_research/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 12:20:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/scribblemaps/geomarketing_market_research/</guid>
      <description>Today we are going to show you some real examples on one of the most advanced functionalities of Scribble Maps:
 Nearby Search.  Any time you have to travel to a new city, you would like to know in a short time, which could be the best area to choose your Hotel, B&amp;amp;B or farmhouse for example.
In order to find it, you would like to point out in your map where the most important services are located as per your interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maps from statistical data</title>
      <link>/post/scribblemaps/maps_from_statistical_data/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 12:20:19 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/scribblemaps/maps_from_statistical_data/</guid>
      <description>Access to weather information has increased enormously. Anyone with a smartphone has an app to check weather forecasts for at any given moment. On a daily basis, we are flooded with information on the internet, TV, and radio about climatic events such as:
 The first snowfall in New York; Milan&amp;rsquo;s airport closing due to fog; Children and the elderly are asked to stay at home during the central hours of the day due to torrid weather.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Thematic Maps Quickly</title>
      <link>/post/scribblemaps/make_thematic_maps_quickly/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 12:19:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/scribblemaps/make_thematic_maps_quickly/</guid>
      <description>Assume that for some reason you need to create some worldwide thematic maps. The maps should contain the national borders, main cities, main communication routes, rivers and lakes. Let us suppose you have a short time to finish the job and you have absolutely nothing at all in your archive. In other words, we have to solve this problem by using only information available on Geospatial Data Portals such as Natural Earth, NASA Earth Observations, The FAO GeoNetwork…, and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn how to create your own custom web maps</title>
      <link>/post/scribblemaps/creating_custom_web_maps/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 12:17:21 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/scribblemaps/creating_custom_web_maps/</guid>
      <description>Since Google Maps released the API in 2005 Web maps became popular after giving web developers an easy way to drop custom apps in their sites with a minimal amount of new code.
Today’s Web maps are known as “slippy maps”. The user can freely pan and zoom in the map with fluid motions. The interface uses Ajax to dynamically load new portions of the map as needed without reloading the whole page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Opendata</title>
      <link>/post/opendata/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 10:19:54 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/opendata/</guid>
      <description>Opendata makes it easy to create a beautiful map for free using QGIS. Customize anything on your map with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Introduction
 A brief introduction to Open Data Intro Open Data Open data as a public asset Open Data Day 2019 Reflections on Why Open Data is not as Simple as it Seems article LinkedIn An exhaustive reference to problems seen in real-world data along with suggestions on how to resolve them Open Data Network  Worldwide</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Display Jupyter Notebooks with Academic</title>
      <link>/post/jupyter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/jupyter/</guid>
      <description>from IPython.core.display import Image Image(&#39;https://www.python.org/static/community_logos/python-logo-master-v3-TM-flattened.png&#39;)  print(&amp;quot;Welcome to Academic!&amp;quot;)  Welcome to Academic!  Install Python and Jupyter Install Anaconda which includes Python 3 and Jupyter notebook.
Otherwise, for advanced users, install Jupyter notebook with pip3 install jupyter.
Create a new blog post as usual Run the following commands in your Terminal, substituting &amp;lt;MY_WEBSITE_FOLDER&amp;gt; and my-post with the file path to your Academic website folder and a name for your blog post (without spaces), respectively:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic: the website designer for Hugo</title>
      <link>/post/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Academic makes it easy to create a beautiful website for free using Markdown. Customize anything on your site with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Follow our easy step by step guide to learn how to build your own free website with Academic. Check out the personal demo or the business demo of what you&amp;rsquo;ll get in less than 10 minutes.
 View the documentation Ask a question Request a feature or report a bug Updating?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>